Okay, so I know that we are in new times, and I know that there's, you know, new efforts and methods always being, you know, put forth.
But why is there a photo contest for a protest?
No Kings is inviting folks to submit their photos from the protest, and a panel of Move On members and staff will select finalists.
Here's the kicker. The winner will be contacted via the email address provided during entry.
This is, this is a surveillance gathering ploy.
The No Kings protests are supported by Hillary Clinton.
Before I even get to her, this is, in those pesky terms and conditions, as a condition of being awarded any prize,
each winner may be required to execute and deliver to sponsor a signed death affidavit of eligibility
and acceptance of these official rules and release of liability,
and any other legal, regulatory, or tax-related documents required by sponsor in its sole discretion.
They're literally making a database of everyone's faces,
and you are actively helping them in doing this.
And you might say, no, Amanda, that's Trump that's making that database.
And the reality is, is that every president that has been in office
has continued to expand the NSA, the CIA, and all of their efforts at invasive surveillance on U.S. citizens.
What many of us are really trying to say about the No Kings is that this is a PSYOP.
And I know many people are saying things like,
if you're not going to No Kings to try to drum up leftist support, then you're a bad leftist,
which, by the way, is an incredibly ridiculous take,
but I'm going to let it slide because it's younger people that said it.
Um, No Kings is supported by the same people that support genocide.
So, the concept of feeling like this is somehow different...
Why am I even making this video?
Do what you want to do.
Just know that you were told.
I would have been out there too, but that would have been in 2008,
and we should know better right now.
Gotta be a better way, and we've gotta...
Gotta be a better way...